const data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which of the following can power our electricity and heat?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Coal",
      "Oil",
      "Gas",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which of the following transportation methods produce the least amount of greenhouse gas emissions?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Taking a bus",
      "Biking",
      "Taking a train",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Walking",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which of the following food can you eat to lower your environmental impact?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Vegetables",
      "Fruits",
      "Whole Grains",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which of the following energy source do airplanes use?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Electrical Energy",
      "Nuclear Energy",
      "Renewable Energy",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Fossil Energy",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following impact does throwing away food bring?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Food rots in a landfill and produces methane",
      "Wasting resources",
      "Wasing energy",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which of the following actions can bring positive impact to the environment?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Shop second-hand clothes",
      "Repair old devices",
      "Donate unwanted items",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which of the following energy sources is renewable?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Wind",
      "Solar",
      "Biomass",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which of the following energy sources does an electric car use?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Fossil Energy",
      "Nuclear Energy",
      "Biomass Energy",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Electrical Energy",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of the following benefits can spending money wisely bring?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Save money!",
      "Support eco-friendly companies",
      "Reduce environmental impact",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which of the following actions can you take to promote climate protection?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Speak up to local leaders",
      "Start the conversation with family, friends and colleagues",
      "Push corporations and politicians to follow the Paris Agreement",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of them!",
  },
];

export default data;